honeytechblog.com 2010-12-14

# Privacy Policy

[Honeytech](http://www.honeytechblog.com/ "Honeytech") Blog is a technology portal of Tutorials, [How to](http://www.honeytechblog.com/tags/how-to/ "How to"), Tips and Guides of [Internet](http://www.honeytechblog.com/tags/internet/ "Internet") Tools, [Social Media](http://www.honeytechblog.com/tags/social-media/ "Social Media"), [Blogging](http://www.blogtechnika.com/top-10-greatest-advantages-of-blogging "Blogging") , WordPress, [Open Source](http://www.honeytechblog.com/topics/open-source/ "Open Source") and Ways to [make money](http://www.honeytechblog.com/topics/money/ "make money") online.  
We have more than **1300 posts** which also provides regular source of updates via Emails and Rss feeds. We are serious on protecting your private data. We have more than 5000 registered members with their personal information safe with us. We assured you that it will only be used to support your relationship with Honeytech Blog. This privacy policy is intended for all users of Honeytechblog.com.

By visiting this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.

On a simple note Honeytechblog.com runs with the back-end of the third partners policies

  * **For Advertisements** appearing on the **Honeytechblog.com** you can refer to [**Google Adsense** privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * **For Visitor tracking y** ou can refer to [**WordPress.com** privacy policies](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and [**GOOGLE ANALYTICS** TERMS OF SERVICE](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html)
  * **For E-mail/RSS updates** you can refer to [**Google Feedburner** Privacy Statement](http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy)

Some common definition of Cookies and Log Files described above are as follows:

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Cookies, if used, will be used on our site to remember and recall login names, login information, previous purchases, potential purchases, as well as other items to help us better understand user’s needs. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the “Profile” section.

We have no control over any third party use also use cookies to store personal information. However, we do not provide this information to any third party.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we may use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Some common FAQ on Honeytechblog.com Privacy Policy**

  * **What personally identifiable information Honeytechblog.com collects.**

We only collect the Name,email address,[contact](http://www.honeytechblog.com/contact/ "contact") information and other info of users that is used in [registering](http://www.honeytechblog.com/wp-login.php?action=register) or contact forms.

  * **What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.**

Already described above (Google Adsense, Feedburner, Analytics and WordPress).

  * **What organization collects the information.**

Already described above (like Google Adsense, Feedburner, Analytics and WordPress).

  * **How Honeytechblog.com uses the information.**

We uses the information only for better communication and relationship with users.

  * **With whom Honeytechblog.com may share user information.**

Already described above (like Google Adsense, Feedburner, Analytics and WordPress).

  * **What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.**

This work is licensed under a [Creative Commons](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/2.5/) © 2006-2010.

  * **What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Honeytechblog.com control.**

We had a regular backup, a dedicated IP and a private SSL installed on our servers. Our site is also enhanced with Content Delivery Network (CDN) from NetDNA.

  * **How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.**

Users can correct any inaccuracies in the profile by just login in their accounts.

At www.honeytechblog.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.honeytechblog.com and how it is used.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Honeytechblog.com via email [admin@honeytechblog.com](mailto:admin@honeytechblog.com). Any violation of this privacy policy will lead to suspension of use privileges and permanent removal from this web site for their IP/ISP.

In case you have anyfurther queries then feel free to [contact here](http://www.honeytechblog.com/contact/)
